Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES V. Affiliates, 1930-80 (Part 1)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES V. AFFILIATES (PART 1)
  - Kentucky
    - Berea
      - Mountain Maternal Health League, Publicity, 1963-1968 (Box 155, Folder 60)
      - Field Trips, 1954-1963 (Box 155, Folder 61)
    - Lexington
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1957
        - 1957-1973 (Box 155, Folder 62)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 155)
      - Affiliation, PP Center, Correspondence from 1955
        - 1955-1973 (Box 155, Folder 63)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 155)
      - Lexington PP Center, Inc., Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1978 (Box 155, Folder 64)
      - PP Center from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 155, Folder 65)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 155)
      - Field Trips, 1954-1960 (Box 155, Folder 66)
      - PP Center, Reports, Members, 1957-1971 (Box 155, Folder 67)
      - PP Center, Reports, Members from 1960
        - 1960-1971 (Box 155, Folder 68)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 155)
      - PP Center, Publicity, 1960-1968 (Box 155, Folder 69)
    - Louisville
      - PP Center, Inc., Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977-1978 (Box 155, Folder 70)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1951
        - 1949-1972 (Box 155, Folder 71)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 155)
      - Affiliation, PP Center, Correspondence from 1950
        - 1950-1973 (Box 155, Folder 72)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 155)
      - PP Center from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 155, Folder 73)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 155)
      - PP Center, Inc., Field Visit Reports, 1976 (Box 155, Folder 74)
      - PP Center, Reports, Clinics, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 75)
      - PP Center, Reports, General, 1960-1969 (Box 155, Folder 76)
      - PP Center, Reports, Members from 1960
        - 1964-1974 (Box 155, Folder 77)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 155)
      - PP Center, Publicity, 1959-1972 (Box 155, Folder 78)
      - PP Clinic, Reports, Manual, 10/1962 (Box 155, Folder 79)
      - Field Trips, 1950-1960 (Box 155, Folder 80)
  - Louisiana
    - Anti-Poverty, 1966-1967 (Box 155, Folder 81)
    - Contacts from 1961
      - 1961-1974 (Box 155, Folder 82)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 155)
    - Family Planning, Inc.; Louisiana Family Planning Program, Inc. from 1968
      - 1967-1974 (Box 155, Folder 83)
      - 1976 (Box 155)
    - Hospitals, General, 1966 (Box 155, Folder 84)
    - Legal, 1957-1965 (Box 155, Folder 85)
    - Public Health, 1964-1969 (Box 155, Folder 86)
    - Public Welfare, 1962-1968 (Box 155, Folder 87)
    - Field Trips, General, 1962-1964 (Box 155, Folder 88)
    - Schools, General, 1972 (Box 155, Folder 89)
    - Tulane University, 1964-1970 (Box 155, Folder 90-92)
  - Maine
    - Field Trips, General, 1953-1961 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Anti-Poverty, 1968 (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Contacts, 1961-1971 (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Family Planning Association of Maine, 1976-1978 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Legal, 1940-1950 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Public Health, 1963-1969 (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Schools, General, 1961-1967 (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Kennebunk, PP, 1964 (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Bangor
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1951-1968 (Box 156, Folder 9)
      - PP, 1967-1968 (Box 156, Folder 10)
      - Field Trips, 1956 (Box 156, Folder 11)
  - Maryland
    - Silver Springs, Field Trips, 1954-1957 (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Anti-Poverty, 1968 (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - Contacts from 1962
      - 1962-1972 (Box 156, Folder 14)
      - 1977 (Box 156)
    - Hospitals, General, 1963-1966 (Box 156, Folder 15)
    - Hospitals, Johns Hopkins, Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 156, Folder 16)
    - Legal, 1923-1969 (Box 156, Folder 17)
    - Migrants, 1963 (Box 156, Folder 18)
    - Public Health, Correspondence, 1961-1969 (Box 156, Folder 19)
    - Public Welfare, 1964-1968 (Box 156, Folder 20)
    - Public Health, Reports and General, 1957-1962 (Box 156, Folder 21)
    - United Fund, United Community Services, 1968 (Box 156, Folder 22)
    - Schools, General, Correspondence, 1964-1970 (Box 156, Folder 23)
    - Johns Hopkins University, Correspondence, 1964-1970 (Box 156, Folder 24)
    - Annapolis, PP Committee, 1959-1962 (Box 156, Folder 25)
    - Baltimore
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1935
        - 1935-1974 (Box 156, Folder 26)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 156)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1959
        - 1959-1974 (Box 156, Folder 27)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 156)
      - PP Association, 1963-74
        - 1970-1974 (Box 156, Folder 28-33)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 156)
      - Field Trips, 1952-1965 (Box 156, Folder 34)
      - PP, Reports, Clinics, 1962 (Box 156, Folder 35)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1962-1968 (Box 156, Folder 36)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1963-1974 (Box 156, Folder 37)
      - PP Association, Publicity, Pamphlets, etc., 1957-1973 (Box 156, Folder 38)
    - Silver Spring
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1949-1960 (Box 156, Folder 39)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence, 1951-1959 (Box 156, Folder 40)
      - PP, 1960-1963 (Box 156, Folder 41)
  - New Mexico
    - Anti-Poverty, 1964-1972 (Box 156, Folder 42)
    - Contacts from 1960
      - 1960-1974 (Box 156, Folder 43)
      - 1975-1980 (Box 156)
    - Legal from 1968
      - 1968-1974 (Box 156, Folder 44)
      - 1978 (Box 156)
    - Migrant, 1962-1974 (Box 156, Folder 45)
    - New Mexico Family Planning Council, 1978-1980 (Box 156, Folder 46)
    - Projects, 1969 (Box 156, Folder 47)
    - Public Health, 1960-1971 (Box 156, Folder 48)
    - Public Welfare, 1965-1968 (Box 156, Folder 49)
    - State-wide Family Planning, 1971-1972 (Box 156, Folder 50)
    - United Fund, 1967 (Box 156, Folder 51)
    - Schools, General, 1969 (Box 156, Folder 52)
    - PPANMA: PP Association of New Mexico Affiliates, 1979 (Box 156, Folder 53)
    - Albuquerque
      - Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1964
        - 1964-1972 (Box 156, Folder 54)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 156)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 156, Folder 55)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 156)
      - Rio Grande PP (formerly Bernalillo County), 1975-1979 (Box 156, Folder 56)
      - PP, 1964-1974 (Box 156, Folder 57-58)
      - Reports, General, 1964-1972 (Box 156, Folder 59)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1964-1974 (Box 156, Folder 60)
      - Publicity from 1964
        - 1967-1973 (Box 156, Folder 61)
        - 1975 (Box 156)
      - Field Trips, 1964-1965 (Box 156, Folder 62)
    - Carlsbad
      - PP Committee, 1962-1967 (Box 156, Folder 63)
      - Field Trips, 1962 (Box 156, Folder 64)
    - Las Cruces
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1962
        - 1962-1973 (Box 156, Folder 65)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 156)
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Correspondence from 1962
        - 1962-1974 (Box 156, Folder 66)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 156)
      - PP of South Central NM, 1976-1979 (Box 156, Folder 67)
      - PP Dona Ana County from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 156, Folder 68)
        - 1975 (Box 156)
      - PP Committee, 1962-1968 (Box 156, Folder 69)
      - Field Trip, 1961-1964 (Box 157, Folder 1)
      - Reports, Clinics from 1967 (empty) (Box 157, Folder 2)
      - PP Association, Reports, General, 1962-1970 (Box 157, Folder 3)
      - PP Association, Reports, Members, 1962-1974 (Box 157, Folder 4)
      - Publicity, 1964-1968 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Sante Fe
      - PP, Maternal, Child and Health Center, 1964-1965 (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Silver City (formerly Fort Bayard)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 157, Folder 7)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 157)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 157, Folder 8)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 157)
      - PP Southwest New Mexico, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1978 (Box 157, Folder 9)
      - PP Southwest New Mexico from 1969
        - 1968-1974 (Box 157, Folder 10)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 157)
      - Publicity, 1972 (Box 157, Folder 11)
      - Reports, General, 1969 (Box 157, Folder 12)
      - Reports, Members, 1969-1974 (Box 157, Folder 13)
  - Massachusetts
    - Anti-Poverty, 1965 (Box 157, Folder 14)
    - Contacts from 1963
      - 1963-1973 (Box 157, Folder 15)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 157)
    - Hospitals, General, 1962-1970 (Box 157, Folder 16)
    - Legal, Booklets, Printed Matter, 1938-1965 (Box 157, Folder 17)
    - Legal, Correspondence, 1938-1972 (Box 157, Folder 18)
    - Projects, 1970 (Box 157, Folder 19)
    - Public Health from 1962
      - 1962-1968 (Box 157, Folder 20)
      - 1975 (Box 157)
    - Public Welfare, 1964 (Box 157, Folder 21)
    - Schools, General, 1964-1972 (Box 157, Folder 22)
    - Boston University from 1963
      - 1963-1969 (Box 157, Folder 23)
      - 1975 (Box 157)
    - Brandeis University, Martin Rein, Reports & Miscellaneous, 1960-1969 (Box 157, Folder 24)
    - Harvard University, Medical, 1961-1969 (Box 157, Folder 25)
    - Harvard University, Center for Population Studies, School of Public Health, 1965-1969 (Box 157, Folder 26)
    - Harvard University, Center for Population Studies, School for Public Health, from 5/63, 1963-1964 (Box 157, Folder 27)
    - Harvard University, General, 1958-1967 (Box 157, Folder 28)
    - Harvard University, Dr. Guttmacher's Trip, 12/7/1962 (Box 157, Folder 29)
    - Harvard University, $2,000 Grant to Dr. William Schmidt for Population Study, 3/62, 1962-1963 (Box 157, Folder 30)
    - Smith College, 1953-1969 (Box 157, Folder 31)
    - Tufts College Medical School, 1964-1968 (Box 157, Folder 32)
    - Cambridge (formerly Boston & Newton Creek)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1948
        - 1948-1974 (Box 157, Folder 33)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 157)
      - Affiliation, PP League of Massachusetts from 1949
        - 1949-1974 (Box 157, Folder 34)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 157)
      - PP League, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978-1979 (Box 157, Folder 35)
      - PP League of Massachusetts, 1976 (Box 157, Folder 36)
    - Newton Center (formerly Boston), PP League of Massachusetts from 1972
      - 1972-1974 (Box 157, Folder 37)
      - 1975 (Box 157)
    - Boston
      - PP League, 1964-1971 (Box 157, Folder 38-39)
      - Field Trips, 1953-1967 (Box 157, Folder 40)
      - PP League, Reports, Clinics, 1966-1967 (Box 157, Folder 41)
      - PP League, Reports, General, 1962-1966 (Box 157, Folder 42)
      - PP League, Reports, Members, 1962-1972 (Box 157, Folder 43)
    - Cambridge, PP League of Massachusetts, Public Affairs, 1977 (Box 157, Folder 44)
    - Boston
      - PP League, Publicity, 1960-1980 (Box 157, Folder 45)
      - Dr. Guttmacher's Trip, 12/5/1962 (Box 157, Folder 46)
    - Catholic Holyoke Incident, 1940-1963 (Box 157, Folder 47)
    - Catholic Historical Referendum, Present Plight, 1942-1954 (Box 157, Folder 48)
    - Pittsfield, PP Association of Berkshire County, 1965-1968 (Box 157, Folder 49)
  - Chicago, Background, 1960-1965 (Box 157, Folder 50)
  - Massachusetts
    - Health, 1966 (Box 157, Folder 51)
    - Legislation, 1965 (Box 157, Folder 52)
    - Newspaper Clips, 1961-1969 (Box 157, Folder 53)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 157, Folder 54)
  - Michigan
    - Abortion Referendum, 1972 (Box 157, Folder 55)
    - Anti-Poverty, 1965-1973 (Box 157, Folder 56)
    - Detroit, C.A.P.S.I.S. (Contraception, Abortion, Pregnancy & Sex Information Services), 1972-1973 (Box 157, Folder 57)
    - Contacts from 1963
      - 1963-1974 (Box 157, Folder 58)
      - 1977 (Box 157)
    - Family Planning Coordinator, Alpina, 1971, (Temporary Folder) (Box 157, Folder 59)
    - Hospitals, General from 1963
      - 1963-1969 (Box 157, Folder 60)
      - 1977 (Box 157)
    - Michigan Coordinating Committee for Abortion Law Reform, 1971 (Box 157, Folder 61)
    - Legal from 1965
      - 1965-1974 (Box 157, Folder 62)
      - 1977-1979 (Box 157)
    - Migrant, 1964-1969 (Box 157, Folder 63)
    - Migrants, Field Trips, 1954 (Box 157, Folder 64)
    - Projects, 1969-1974 (Box 157, Folder 65)
    - "Publicity Funded Family Planning Programs in Michigan," A Report by the Health Impact Project, 8/30/1972 (Box 157, Folder 66)
    - Public Health from 1963
      - 1963-1974 (Box 158, Folder 1)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 158)
    - Public Welfare, 1963-1970 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - United Fund, 1968-1971 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Schools, General, 1963-1974 (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Schools, The Merrill-Palmer School, Detroit, 1961-1965 (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Schools, Michigan State University, East Lansing, 1963-1974 (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - Schools, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor from 1963
      - 1963-1974 (Box 158, Folder 7)
      - 1976-1979 (Box 158)
    - Schools, University of Michigan, Center for Population Plng, Ann Arbor, 1962-1971 (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Michigan PP Affiliates Committee (MPPAC), 1971-1972 (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - Minutes, MPPC: (Michigan Planned Parenthood Council), 1972-1974 (Box 158, Folder 10)
    - PP Affiliates of Michigan (formerly Michigan Planned Parenthood Council) from 1974
      - 1972-1974 (Box 158, Folder 11)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 158)
    - Planned Parenthood Council, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 158, Folder 12)
    - Ann Arbor
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1948
        - 1949-1974 (Box 158, Folder 13)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 158)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1963
        - 1963-1965 (Box 158, Folder 14)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 158)
      - Field Trips, 1952-1960 (Box 158, Folder 15)
      - Washtenaw County League for PP, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 158, Folder 16)
      - PP of Washtenaw County, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 158, Folder 17)
      - PP, 1967-1969 (Box 158, Folder 18)
      - Washtenaw County League for PP from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 158, Folder 19)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 158)
      - PP, 1964-1966 (Box 158, Folder 20)
      - PP Washtenaw County: Injunction, Use of PP/WP Trademark, Betty Eason, 1979 (Box 158, Folder 21)
      - PP, Reports, Clinics, 1961-1968 (Box 158, Folder 22)
      - Reports, General, 1964-1969 (Box 158, Folder 23)
      - PP, Reports, Members from 1963 (Box 158)
        - 1963-1974 (Box 157, Folder 24)
        - 1976 (Box 157)
      - PP, Publicity, 1963-1971 (Box 157, Folder 25)
      - Washtenaw League for PP, Public Affairs, 1976 (Box 157, Folder 26)
    - Benton Harbor
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1969
        - 1969-1972 (Box 157, Folder 27)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 157)
      - Affiliation, Twin Cities PP Association, Correspondence from 1969
        - 1969-1973 (Box 157, Folder 28)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 157)
      - PP Association of Southwestern Michigan from 1968
        - 1968-1974 (Box 157, Folder 29)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 157)
      - Reports, Members from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 157, Folder 30)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 157)
      - Publicity, undated (Box 157, Folder 31)
    - Birmingham
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1958-1960 (Box 157, Folder 32)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence, 1956-1959 (Box 157, Folder 33)
      - PP, 1958-1960 (Box 157, Folder 34)
      - Oakland Chapter, 1954-1960 (Box 157, Folder 35)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1958-1960 (Box 157, Folder 36)
      - PP, Publicity, 1960-1963 (Box 157, Folder 37)
    - Detroit
      - Affiliation, PP League, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws
        - 1970-1973 (Box 157, Folder 38)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 157)
      - Affiliation, PP League, Budgets, Audits, Bylaws, 1948-1968 (Box 157, Folder 39)
      - Affiliation, PP League, Correspondence
        - 1970-1974 (Box 157, Folder 40)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 157)
      - Affiliation, PP League, Correspondence, 1949-1969 (Box 157, Folder 41)
      - PP League from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 157, Folder 42)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 157)
      - PP League, 1965-1970 (Box 157, Folder 43)
      - PP League, 1963-1964 (Box 157, Folder 44)
      - PP League, Inc., Confidential, Controversy: Hew, Personnel, Clinic Closing, 1975-1976 (Box 157, Folder 45)
      - Field Trips, 1956-1963 (Box 157, Folder 46)
      - PP League, Reports, Clinics from 1969
        - 1969 (Box 157, Folder 47)
        - 1975 (Box 157)
      - PP League, Reports, General, 1962-1969 (Box 157, Folder 48)
      - Publicity, 1962-1976 (Box 157, Folder 49)
      - PP League, Reports, Members from 1960
        - 1963-1974 (Box 157, Folder 50)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 157)
    - Flint
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1963
        - 1964-1972 (Box 157, Folder 51)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 157)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence from 1963
        - 1963-1972 (Box 157, Folder 52)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 157)
      - (Flint Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977) (Box 157, Folder 53)
      - Flint Community PP Association from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 157, Folder 54)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 157)
      - PP, 1964-1968 (Box 159, Folder 1-2)
      - Flint Community PP Association, Chapters from 1971
        - 1971 (Box 159, Folder 3)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 159)
      - Flint Community PP Association, Filed Visit Records, 1977 (Box 159, Folder 4)
      - Field Trips, 1957-1964 (Box 159, Folder 5)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1964-1969 (Box 159, Folder 6)
      - PP, Reports, Members from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 159, Folder 7)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 159)
      - PP, Publicity, 1963-1965 (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Grand Rapids
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1964
        - 1964-1973 (Box 159, Folder 9)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 159)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence
        - 1965-1974 (Box 159, Folder 10)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 159)
      - PP Association of Kent County, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977-1978 (Box 159, Folder 11)
      - PP Kent County from 1966
        - 1966-1974 (Box 159, Folder 12)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 159)
      - PP Kent County, 1964-1965 (Box 159, Folder 13)
      - PP Association Kent County, Chapters from 1973
        - 1973 (Box 159, Folder 14)
        - 1975 (Box 159)
      - Field Trips from 9/64, 1964-1965 (Box 159, Folder 15)
      - PP, Kent County Branch, Center Handbook, 1978 (Box 159, Folder 16)
      - PP, Reports, Clinics, 1965 (Box 159, Folder 17)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1964-1967 (Box 159, Folder 18)
      - PP, Reports, Members from 1964
        - 1964-1973 (Box 159, Folder 19)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 159)
      - PP, Reports, Publicity, 1964-1966 (Box 159, Folder 20)
    - Kalamazoo
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, Reproductive Health Care Center, 1977-1978 (Box 159, Folder 21)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1966
        - 1966-1974 (Box 159, Folder 22)
        - 1980 (Box 159)
      - Affiliation, Reproductive Health Care Center of South Central Michigan, Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 159, Folder 23)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1966 (Box 159, Folder 24)
      - Reproductive Health Care Center of South Central Michigan, Legal, 1978-1979 (Box 159, Folder 25)
      - Reproductive Health Care Center, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 159, Folder 26)
      - Merger, 1977 (Box 159, Folder 27)
      - Reproductive Health Care Center of South Central Michigan, 1977-1979 (Box 159, Folder 28)
      - PP from 1966
        - 1965-1974 (Box 159, Folder 29)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 159)
      - PP Association Kalamazoo County, Chapters, 1972 (Box 159, Folder 30)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1967 (Box 159, Folder 31)
      - PP, Reports, Members from 1966
        - 1966-1974 (Box 159, Folder 32)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 159)
      - Field Trips, 1948-1952 (Box 159, Folder 33)
    - Lansing
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1969-1973 (Box 159, Folder 34)
      - Affiliation, PP Association of Greater Lansing, Correspondence from 1968
        - 1968-1973 (Box 159, Folder 35)
        - 1975 (Box 159)
      - PP Association of Greater Lansing, 1967-1973 (Box 159, Folder 36)
      - Reports, Members, 1969-1970 (Box 159, Folder 37)
    - Monroe
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1967-1974 (Box 159, Folder 38)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1967
        - 1967-1974 (Box 159, Folder 39)
        - 1975 (Box 159)
      - PP Monroe County, 1967-1973 (Box 159, Folder 40)
      - PP Monroe County, Reports, Members, 1969-1971 (Box 159, Folder 41)
    - Muskegon
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1967
        - 1967-1974 (Box 159, Folder 42)
        - 1980 (Box 159)
      - Affiliation, Muskegon Area PP, Correspondence from 1967
        - 1967-1974 (Box 159, Folder 43)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 159)
      - Muskegon Area PP Assoc, Inc., Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 159, Folder 44)
      - Muskegon Area Planned Parenthood from 1965
        - 1963-1974 (Box 159, Folder 45)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 159)
      - Reports, General, 1965-1967 (Box 159, Folder 46)
      - Reports, Members from 1966
        - 1966-1974 (Box 159, Folder 47)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 159)
      - Publicity, 1965 (Box 159, Folder 48)
    - Petoskey
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 159, Folder 49)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 159)
      - Affiliation, Northern Michigan PP, Correspondence from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 159, Folder 50)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 159)
      - Northern Michigan PP Association, Legal, 1978 (Box 159, Folder 51)
      - Petoskey Traverse City PP, Merger, 1972-1973 (Box 159, Folder 52)
      - Northern Michigan PP Association from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 159, Folder 53)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 159)
      - Reports, Members, 1971 (Box 159, Folder 54)
      - Northern Michigan PP Association, Chapters from 1973
        - 1973-1974 (Box 159, Folder 55)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 159)
    - Saginaw
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1965-1971 (Box 159, Folder 56)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence, 1965-1974 (Box 159, Folder 57)
      - Planned Parenthood, 1964-1973 (Box 159, Folder 58)
      - Field Trips from 9/1964 (Box 159, Folder 59)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1966-1970 (Box 159, Folder 60)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1965-1971 (Box 159, Folder 61)
      - PP, Publicity, 1965 (Box 159, Folder 62)
    - Traverse City
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1970-1973 (Box 159, Folder 63)
      - Affiliation, Traverse City Area PP, Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 159, Folder 64)
      - Traverse City Area PP, 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 159, Folder 65)
        - 1975 (Box 159)
    - Field Trips, General, 1954-1965 (Box 159, Folder 66)
  - Minnesota
    - Anti-Poverty, 1965-1971 (Box 159, Folder 67)
    - Contacts, 1963-1972 (Box 159, Folder 68)
    - Hospitals, General, 1964-1967 (Box 159, Folder 69)
    - Legal, 1965-1973 (Box 159, Folder 70)
    - Migrant, 1962-1965 (Box 159, Folder 71)
    - Minnesota Council on Illegitimacy, Survey Report on Young Unmarried Mothers Who Keep Children, 1969 (Box 159, Folder 72)
    - Projects, 1969-1971 (Box 159, Folder 73)
    - PERC of Minnesota: Public Education & Research Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 159, Folder 74)
    - Public Health, 1963-1969 (Box 159, Folder 75)
    - Public Welfare, 1963-1969 (Box 159, Folder 76)
    - (State) Schools, 1963-1971 (Box 159, Folder 77)
    - (State) Schools, University of Minnesota, 1964-1971 (Box 159, Folder 78)
    - Minneapolis
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1954-1962 (Box 159, Folder 79)
      - PP, 1963-1971 (Box 160, Folder 1)
      - PP, 1968 (Box 160, Folder 2)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence, 1958-1969 (Box 160, Folder 3)
      - Minnesota PP, 1967 (Box 160, Folder 4)
      - PP, 1965-1966 (Box 160, Folder 5)
      - PP, 1964-1965 (Box 160, Folder 6)
      - Field Trips, 1952-1962 (Box 160, Folder 7)
      - PP, Reports, Clinics, 1963-1969 (Box 160, Folder 8)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1963-1969 (Box 160, Folder 9)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1964-1970 (Box 160, Folder 10)